Here's step-by-step instructions to use the program:
1. Open the Command Line for your Operating System (Cmd on Windows).

2. Change your directory to the project directory's "src" folder.

3. Type and enter 'javac *.java' to compile the classes necessary to run the program.
 
(Note: I have to type 'javac --release 8 *.java' in order to run the program on my computer so please do so if you're experiencing issues)


4. Then enter 'java Main' to start playing Checkers against the computer! The game works as follows:
- You are black, the AI is red
- In order to move you must first provide a start coordinate i.e. 'A6', then press enter. Now give the coordinate of the space you wish to move to i.e. 'B5'.
- When you are next to an enemy that you can jump, you must take the jump. In order to do so: select the piece by supplying the start coordinate, then enter the coordinate of the piece you wish to jump (NOT THE SQUARE YOUR PIECE IS GOING TO END UP IN). The console will inform you if you can make a second jump afterwards.
- The game ends when you win, or the computer does.
- You may also end the game by typing 'end', 'stop' or 'no' at any point during your turn.
